Rin.
Yes?
What present would you like Santa Claus to bring you?
I haven't thought about it yet.
He won't make it if you don't think of something quick.
He's coming from really far away.
I see...
Let's hear it. What do you want the most now?
A Lob Ear.
What? Don't you already have that?
She wants friends.
Good evening!
Sorry for coming so late.
Don't worry about it.
Rin-chan!
What's that?
This is a Christmas tree.
What about this one?
Well... some stuff from work.
Let's put up the tree.
Hurry up! Daikichi!
Coming~!
This one goes on the top?
Yep.
What's wrong?
Our house doesn't have a chimney.
Santa Claus will have his own way of getting in,
so don't worry about it.
I'll unlock the door then.
No need for that.
To Santa Claus, thank you for the present.
What's with that carrot?
That's for Mr. Reindeer.
I'm switching off the lights.
A little while more.
Santa Claus won't come unless you go to sleep.
What?! Hurry and turn off the lights!
As you wish.
To Santa Claus, thank you for the present.
Rin
I wanted to meet Santa Claus, too.
Rin, time to eat.
OK~!
Thanks to Mr. Reindeer too.
「 To Santa Claus 」